Guide to the Widmer Wine Cellars Records,1906-1963.
Widmer Wine Cellars Records
- Giron & Torres, Sucr., 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- G - Grape Juices, Grape Prices, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- The Grape Juice Producers Association, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- H, 1919, 1933-1936 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- I, 1933-1935 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Inventory, 1922-1923 (Box 9, Folder 68)
- K, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 69)
- Internal Revenue Service, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 70)
- Inventories, 1917, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 71)
- Jelly, 1933-1934 (Box 9, Folder 72)
- Jackson, Zaenglein & Ellis, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- K, 1932-1934 (Box 9, Folder 74)
- L, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 75)
- Lash, Inc., 1933 (Box 9, Folder 76)
- New York State, 1925-1935 (Box 9, Folder 77-78)
- M, 1930-1936 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
- L. B. Montfort - General, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- L. B. Montfort, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- L. B. Montfort, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- N, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Naples Village, 1929-1931 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- National Grape Juice Co., 1924-1926 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- National Recovery Act, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- National Testing Lab - Analysis, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 10-11)
- National Testing Lab - Analysis, 1929-1930 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- National Testing Lab - Correspondence, 1928-1932 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- National Testing Lab - Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 14-15)
- P, 1933-1935 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- R, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- S, 1931-1935 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- T, 1915, 1919, 1932-1935 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Trade Marks (Midas -Mason, Fenwick & Lawrence - Montfort), 1919, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- U, 1931-1935 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Wisconsin, 1933-1935 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- U..S. - Alcohol Control Administration Releases, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- U. S. Internal Revenue Service, 1922-1932 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- U.S. Treasury, 1926-1927 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- U.S. Treasury, 1928-1929 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- U.S. Treasury, 1930-1931 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- U.S. Treasury, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- U.S. Treasury, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 29-30)
- U.S. Treasury, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- U.S. Treasury, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 32-33)
- Virginia, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- W, 1917, 1933-1935 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Widmer.s Wine Tonic, 1921, 1932-1935 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Wine Tonic, 1925-1933 (Box 10, Folder 37-38)
- Widmer's Grape Product Industry and Wine Cellars, Inc., 1931-1933 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Welch Grape Juice, 1933-1935 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Zucker, Steiner & Co., 1917-1934 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Alfred Lawrence, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Aetna Life Ins., 1945 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- A, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- A, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Alabama, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- S, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Pfaulder Co., 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- P, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Schoonmaker & Co., 1944 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- T, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- U, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- V, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Widmer's - Letters from Employees in Service, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Widmer, Carl, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Clippings, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Coats & Burchard Co., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Harry Cohen, 1937-1943 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Corporation Trust Co. - Michigan, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Crowder, LeRoy W., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Fire, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Grapes, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Italian Swiss Colony, 1942-1945 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- McDougal & Co., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 64)
- McGarrahan, Frank, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 65)
- MacGowen, James, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 66)
- Montfort, Louis, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 67)
- N, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 68)
- Neithercott, Barry N., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Pamphlets and Clippings, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Pfaudler Co., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 71)
- D. W. Putnam - Grape Juice, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 72)
- P, Q, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 73)
- Rationing Wine, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 74)
- Processed Food Monthly Report, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 75)
- S, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 76)
- Schoomaker - NYC and San Fransisco, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 77)
- "21" Brands Inc., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 78)
- Street Julian, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 79)
- W, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 80)
- Urbana Wine Co., Inc., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 81)
- U.S. Treasury Dept., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 82)
- U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 83)
- U.S. Bureau of Internal Revenue, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 84)
- U.S. Alcohol Tax Unit - NYC, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 85)
- W, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 86)
- Arvin Awine Co., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 87)
- Archer, George, 1942-1944 (Box 10, Folder 88)
- California Products, 1942-1945 (Box 10, Folder 89)
- Central Winery, Inc., 1942 (Box 10, Folder 90)
- Crowder, LeRoy, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Defense Supplies Corporation, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- G, 1942-1943 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Grape Juice, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- MacGowen, James - Brokerage, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- McGarrahan, Francis J., 1942 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- McDougall & Co., 1942 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Martini, L. M., 1943 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Montfort, Louis, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- National Testing Laboratory, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- P, Q, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Rubenstein, Mrs. Irene, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Schoonmaker, Frank - New York City, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 13-15)
- S, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Universal Wine & Liquor, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Urbana Wine, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- U.S. Bureau of, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- U.S. Bureau of Interanl Revenue, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Wine Institute Releases, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- U.S.F.A.A. - Washington, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Tolhurst Extractor, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- New York State Department of Agriculture, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Horix Manufacturing Company, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Jackson, Zaenlein, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Keeler, E. Co., 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Keotz Machine, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Legal Forms and Papers, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Mayer Tank Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Montfort, Louis B., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Pfaudler Co., 1941 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- U.S. Internal Revenue - Alcohol Tax Unit, 1940-1941 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Walker-Wallace, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Kaplan, J. M., 1940 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Laurence, Alfred, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Montfort, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- National Grape Corporation, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- National Testing Laboratory, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Pamphlets, etc., 1940 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- U.S. Internal Revenue, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- American Grape Juice Co., 1939 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Aetna, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Brewer, Gil - Broadcasts, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- C, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Grape Juice Contracts - Completed, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- De Laval Separator Co., 1939 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- F, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- G, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Gooch & Co., 1939 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Gooch & C o. Recipes, etc., 1939 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- H, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- I, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- J, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Labels, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- K, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- L, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 58)
- Lefler, Harry, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 59)
- Laurence, Alfred, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 60)
- M, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 61)
- Monftort, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 62)
- N, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 63)
- P, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 64)
- Pamphlets, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 65-67)
- R, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 68)
- Schoonmaker, Frank & C., 1939 (Box 11, Folder 69)
- Sharples Corp., 1939 (Box 11, Folder 70)
- T, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 71)
- U, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 72)
- Virginia, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 73)
- W, 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 74)
- A, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 75)
- Aluminum Co. of America, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 76)
- Baldwin & Strachan, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 77)
- Bock, E. C., 1938 (Box 11, Folder 78-79)
- Budde & Westerman, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 80)
- Barry-Wehmiller Machinery Co., 1938 (Box 11, Folder 81)
- C, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 82)
- Canners Exchange, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 83)
- D, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 84)
- Dun & Bradstreet - Reports, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 85)
- E, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 86)
- Finger Lakes Wine Growers, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 87)
- Grapes, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 88)
- Grape Products Association, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 89)
- Gooch & Co., 1938 (Box 11, Folder 90)
- H, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 91)
- Haverstock & Co., 1938 (Box 11, Folder 92)
- Iowa, State of, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 93)
- Jackson, Zaenglein & Ellis, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 94)
- K, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 95)
- Lefler, Harry, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 96)
- Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 97)
- Licenses, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 98)
- M, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
- Machinery, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Mayer Tank Manufacturing Co., 1938 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- L. M. Martin Grape Products, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Michigan, Minnesota, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Montfort, Louis B., 1938 (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
- N, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- National Testing Laboratory, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- North Carolina, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- O, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Owens-Illinois, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Photos, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- P, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Pamphlets and Clippings, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Pennsylvania Liquor Control Board, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- R, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- S, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- T, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- U.S. - Alcohol Tax Unit, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- U.S. - Federal Alcohol Administration, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- U.S. - Federal Trade Commissions and U.S. Congress, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- U.S. - FAA label Disapprovals, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- U.S. - Internal Revenue, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- U.S.. Department Labor: Agriculture, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Urbana Wine Co., 1938 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Utica Mutual Insurance Co., 1938 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- V, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- W, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Wells, B. H., 1938 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Wrasse, H. R., 1938 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- X, Y, Z, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Grape Juice - Berliner Report, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Concord Grape Co-op Development Assn. - Penn Yan - Annual Report, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Concord Grape Co-op Assn. - Dunkirk Report, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 36-37)
- Sharples, 1949, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Cider - Berliner Report, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Progress Report from the Pilot Plant - Concord Grape Co-op Development Assn. - Penn Yan, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Concord Grape Co-op Cevelopment Assn - Penn Yan - Annual Report, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Clippings, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Licenses, Memos, etc., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- A, B, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- C, D, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Calkins & Co., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Cole, Sander W., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- E, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- F, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Ferguson Bedell Co., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- G, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Geron & Torres, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- H, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- I-L, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Kennedy Menke Co., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- Alfred Laurence, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- McGowan, James, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- M, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 58-59)
- McGarrahan, Frank, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- Moran, Raymond, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- N, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- O, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- P, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 64)
- Powell, W. D., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 65-66)
- Platter, Charles & Co., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 67)
- S, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 68-69)
- R, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 70)
- Simon, Sol, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 71)
- Sol Simon Contracts with Monarch Wine Corp., 1950-1954 (Box 12, Folder 72)
- T, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 73)
- W, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 74)
- Walsh, James N., Co.. Inc., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 75)
- Widmer's Wine, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Brokers Convention, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- A, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Addison Lithograph, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Application Salesmen, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- B, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Baldwin & Strachan, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Bardenheir, John, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- C, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- District of Columbia, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- D, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- E, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- F, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Salesmen - Form Letters, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- G, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- H, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- I, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- J, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- K, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- L, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Lefler, Harry, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Maine, State of, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- McAuliffe, M. L., 1952 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- McGarrahan, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- N, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- New York State Agricultural Experiment Station, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- New York State Department of Labor, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Neithercott, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- O, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Owens-Illinois Glass, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- P, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Pamphlets, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Pfaudler Co., 1952 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- R, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- S, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Sforzini, L., 1952 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- T, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- U, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Utica Mutual Insurance, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- V, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- W, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Wine Institute Correspondence, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Warner, Lansing B., 1952 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- X,Y,Z, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Crown Cork & Seal, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- A, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- B, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Catalogs, Wine Booklets, etc., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 48)
- D, 1950-1954 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- E, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- C, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 51)
- F, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Form Letters, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 53)
- G, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- H, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 55)
- K, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 56)
- L, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 57)
- M, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- N, 1937-1952 (Box 13, Folder 59)
- P, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 60-62)
- R, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 63)
- S, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 64)
- Salesmen, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 65)
- T, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 66)
- U, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 67)
- W, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 68)
- Widmer Will, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 69)
- A, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 70)
- B, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 71)
- C, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 72)
- D, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 73)
- E, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 74)
- F, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 75)
- G, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 76)
- L, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 77)
- Laurence, Alfred, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 78)
- McGowan, James W., 1949 (Box 13, Folder 79)
- McGarrahan, Frank, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 80)
- M, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 81)
- N, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 82)
- Neithercott, H.R., 1949 (Box 13, Folder 83)
- O, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 84)
- P, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 85)
- Powell, W.D., 1949 (Box 13, Folder 86)
- R, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 87)
- S, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 88)
- T, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 89)
- Simons, Sol, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Southwest Brokerage Co., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Salesmen's Form Letters, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Trant's Inc., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Walsh, James M. Co., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Eyer, Grant, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Frost, Thomas, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Laurence, Alfred, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Pooler, Guy, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Powell, W.D., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Spoor, Douglas, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Widmer's Wine Cellars, Inc. (Kolsan), 1953 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Addison Lithograph, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- A, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- American, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Applications - Office, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Automatic Combustion Co., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- B, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Baldwin, Bowers & Atrachen, Inc., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Bardenheier, John, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Bedford Products, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Beverage Distributors, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- C, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- California Grape Products, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Christmas Card List, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Complaints, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- D, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Donations, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- E, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- F, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- G, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Grapes, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Grape Brush, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Ethnic German Family - Abram Teichrib, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Ethnic Germans - Jacob Ruppert, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Ethnic Germans - Cancelled - Rejected - Closed Cases, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Ethnic Germans - Jilling, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Ethnic German - Huber Family, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- H, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Hercules Filter Company, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Holterbosch, Hans, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Inquiries - Export, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Irving Trust, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Jersey National Liquor, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- J, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Kansas, State of, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- K, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Labels, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 48)
- Lefler, Harry, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- L, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- M, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 51-52)
- Monarch Wine Corp. - M. Coven, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- Mundet Cork Co., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Maine, State of, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Maryland, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Massachusetts, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Mcdougal & Co., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 58)
- McKesson & Robbins, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- Michigan, State of, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- N, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 61)
- National Tax Equality, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 62)
- National Testing Laboratory, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- New York State, Medical Society of, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 64)
- New Y ork State Agricutural Experiment Station, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 65)
- New York State Canners Association, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- New York State Liquor Authority, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 67-68)
- New York State Department of Taxation, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 69)
- New York State - General, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 70)
- New York State Department of Labor, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 71)
- New Jersey, State of, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 72)
- New York State Wine company, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 73)
- North Carolina, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 74)
- Ohio, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 75)
- Ohio Wine Dealers Association, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 76)
- Ontario County, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 77)
- Owens-Illinois Glass, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 78)
- O, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 79)
- Pamphlets and Clippings, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 80-81)
- Paul, Nick, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 82)
- P, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 83)
- Pennsylvania, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 84)
- Pfaudler Co., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 85)
- Pneumatic Scale Corp., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 86)
- R, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 87)
- Sparkler Manufacturing Co., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 88)
- S, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 89)
- T, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 90)
- Taylor Wine Co., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 91)
- Try-Me Bottling Co., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 92)
- U, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 93)
- U.S. Bid Invitations, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 94)
- U.S. Commisioner of Internal Revenue, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 95)
- U.S. - General, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 96)
- Urbana Wine, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 97)
- U.S. - Alcohol Tax Unit, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 98)
- U.S. Army Grape Juice, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 99)
- Utah, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 100)
- Utica Mutual Insurance Co., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 101)
- U.S. Collector of Internal Revenue, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 102)
- V, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 103)
- Virginia ABC Board, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 104)
- W, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 105)
- Witt, John, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 106)
- Walker-Wallace, 193 (Box 14, Folder 107)
- Warren, Lansing B., 1953 (Box 14, Folder 108)
- Welcome Wagon Reports, Babytime, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 109)
- West Virginia, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 110)
- Invoices, 1910-1914 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Old Permits and Original of Blue Print, 1923-1933 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- NY L-128 (permit) and V-2 Matters, 1930-1933 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- NY H2 Permits and Labels (sauces, jellies, etc.), 1930-1933 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Permits, 1930-1933 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Storage Plans, 1930-1933 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Photos, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- H-25097 Special (permit), 1933 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Permit (photocopies), 1933 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Permit NYA-263 W.W.C. Inc., 1933-1935 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- National Industrial Recovery Administration, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- MacDougal - Youngs, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Ethnic Germans, 1949-1954 (Box 15, Folder 13-14)
- Canton Barrel & Bag, Inc., 1949-1955 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Photographs (tax matters), 1924 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Photographs - Wine Bottles, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Records, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
- Records, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 4-6)
- John Bardenheier Wine & Liquor, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- B, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Booklets, Clippings, etc., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- C, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Complaints re Closures, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Complaints - Wine, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 12-13)
- D, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- E, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- F, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- G, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- H, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- L, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- M, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- McGarrahan, Frank, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- New York State Grape Industry, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- New York State, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- W. D. Powell, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- R, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- S, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Salesmen and New York Warehouse (Kolsan), 1955 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Hubert C. Stollenwerk, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- T, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- United States, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Wine Bottling Wine, ca.1955 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Statements, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Statements, Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Statements, Reports, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 34-35)
- Reports, Minutes, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 36-37)
- Minutes, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Permit New York K-310, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 40)
  Includes recipe cards, Widmer Group Insurance booklet, an act about liquor traffic.
- Invoice: Ph. Braun Mainz, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Estimates, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Press Plant Conversion, 1953-1958 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Bunch count, 1953-1961 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Estimates, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Grape Juice, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Estimates, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Reed Property, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Grape Estimate - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Grape Growers - D. Hawk, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Boiler, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Grape Estimate - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Reed Temperature, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Grapes - 1960 and older, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Grapes, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
- Labels, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Brochures, holiday card, newspaper clipping, ca. 1952, 1956, 1970, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Photographs of a presentation to the New York State Agricultural Experiment Station by Widmer executives. Includes a photo of Dr. John Einset., September 1977 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Oversize Photographs including Panorama from Sherman Hill, Naples, New York, 1936, 1936 (Mapcase-folder 1)